https://www.nacbt.org/cookie-policy-us/

Cookie Policy (US) – National Association of Cognitive-Behavioral Therapists
CBT: Cognitive-Behavioral Therapy Fidelity Measurement
Why CBT?
Five Most Common Reasons CBT Fails
For Everyone
Cognitive-Behavioral Therapy Webinars
What is Cognitive-Behavioral Therapy?
FAQs
Cookie Policy (US)
Search for:
Main Menu
Cookie Policy (US)
This page was last changed on April 23, 2020, last checked on April 23, 2020 and applies to citizens of the United States. 1. IntroductionOur website, https://www.nacbt.org (hereinafter: "the website") uses cookies and other related technologies (for convenience all technologies are referred to as "cookies"). Cookies are also placed by third parties we have engaged. In the document below we inform you about the use of cookies on our website.2. What are cookies?A cookie is a small simple file that is sent along with pages of this website and stored by your browser on the hard drive of your computer or another device. The information stored therein may be returned to our servers or to the servers of the relevant third parties during a subsequent visit.3. What are scripts?A script is a piece of program code that is used to make our website function properly and interactively. This code is executed on our server or on your device.4. What is a web beacon?A web beacon (or a pixel tag) is a small, invisible piece of text or image on a website that is used to monitor traffic on a website. In order to do this, various data about you is stored using web beacons.5. ConsentWhen you visit our website for the first time, we will show you a pop-up with an explanation about cookies. You do have the right to opt-out and to object against the further use of non-functional cookies.Revoke cookie consent Current status: AcceptedCurrent status: DeniedYou can also disable the use of cookies via your browser, but please note that our website may no longer work properly.6. Cookies6.1 Technical or functional cookiesSome cookies ensure that certain parts of the website work properly and that your user preferences remain known. By placing functional cookies, we make it easier for you to visit our website. This way, you do not need to repeatedly enter the same information when visiting our website and, for example, the items remain in your shopping cart until you have paid. We may place these cookies without your consent.6.2 Advertising cookiesOn this website we use advertising cookies, enabling us to gain insights into the campaign results. This happens based on a profile we create based on your behavior on https://www.nacbt.org. With these cookies you, as website visitor are linked to a unique ID, but will not profile your behavior and interests to serve personalized ads.You can object to the tracking by these cookies by clicking the "Revoke cookie consent" button.6.3 Social media buttonsOn our website we have included buttons for Facebook and Twitter to promote webpages (e.g. “like”, “pin”) or share (e.g. “tweet”) on social networks like Facebook and Twitter. These buttons work using pieces of code coming from Facebook and Twitter themselves. This code places cookies. These social media buttons also can store and process certain information, so a personalized advertisement can be shown to you.Please read the privacy statement of these social networks (which can change regularly) to read what they do with your (personal) data which they process using these cookies. The data that is retrieved is anonymized as much as possible. Facebook and Twitter are located in the United States.7. Placed cookiesCleanTalk Spam Protect
We use CleanTalk Spam Protect for spam prevention. Read more
Name
Retention
Function
Functional
apbct_site_landing_ts
ct_checkjs
apbct_visible_fields
ct_fkp_timestamp
Sharing
For more information, please read the CleanTalk Spam Protect Privacy Policy.Cerber Security & Anti-Spam
We use Cerber Security & Anti-Spam for website security. Read more
Name
Retention
Function
Functional
cerber_groove
1 year
Provide protection against hackers
cerber_groove_x_*
2 weeks
Provide protection against hackers
Sharing
For more information, please read the Cerber Security & Anti-Spam Privacy Policy.Twitter
We use Twitter for display of recent social posts and/or social share buttons. Read more
Name
Retention
Function
Functional
local_storage_support_test
persistent
Load balancing functionality
Marketing/Tracking
metrics_token
persistent
Stores if the user has seen embedded content
Sharing
For more information, please read the Twitter Privacy Policy.Miscellaneous
Name
Retention
Function
Purpose pending investigation
host-extension-contentDocumentStart.js-rev
host-extension-contentDocumentStart.js
ct_cookies_test
spu_closing
Sharing
This data is not shared with third parties.8. Your rights with respect to personal dataYou have the following rights with respect to your personal data:
you may submit a request for access to the data we process about you;
you may object to the processing;
you may request an overview, in a commonly used format, of the data we process about you;
you may request correction or deletion of the data if it is incorrect or not or no longer relevant, or to ask to restrict the processing of the data.
To exercise these rights, please contact us. Please refer to the contact details at the bottom of this cookie statement. If you have a complaint about how we handle your data, we would like to hear from you.9. Enabling/disabling and deleting cookiesYou can use your internet browser to automatically or manually delete cookies. You can also specify that certain cookies may not be placed. Another option is to change the settings of your internet browser so that you receive a message each time a cookie is placed. For more information about these options, please refer to the instructions in the Help section of your browser.10. Selling data to third partiesWe do not sell data to third parties11. Contact detailsFor questions and/or comments about our cookie policy and this statement, please contact us by using the following contact details:National Association of Cognitive-Behavioral Therapists
P.O. Box 2195
Weirton, WV 26062
United States
Website: https://www.nacbt.org
Email: nacbt@nacbt.org
This cookie policy was synchronized with cookiedatabase.org on April 23, 2020
Share This:
Copyright © 2020 National Association of Cognitive-Behavioral Therapists.
Powered by WordPress and HitMag.
We encourage you to visit our CBT Online Store for excellent home study training programs and CBT self-help programs.
http://nacbt.americommerce.com
Mental Health Professionals! Sign-up for our email newsletter and you will be registered to win an NACBT home study program. One home study program is randomly awarded each month.
Subscribe to our mailing list
